

 $\bowtie$ 

wzhu66@hku.hk



Sai Wan, Hong Kong



+852 52260730



https://weizhudesign.github.io/

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML5

CSS

Javascript

Wordpress

Moodle

Microsoft Office Set

**jQuery** 

PHP

MySQL

Node JS

# **LANGUAGES**

Mandarin (native speaker)























# WEI ZHU (Jo Zhu)

Web Developer & Multimedia Designer

Professional, task-driven web developer with 3 years experience in front end development and 5+ years in Art and Design. Proficient in developing user inferface, improving user experience, designing databases, writing and testing codes, troubleshooting all different issues related to web.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Web developer/Graphic designer (Assistant Multimedia Developement Officer)

Faculty of Social Sciences, the University of Hong Kong.

(06/2021 - present)

- Responsible for front end design and set up of an Virtual Learning & Teaching Platform (an one stop shop for faculty student and teachers).
- Setting up LearningLocker LRS(learning record store) system on Ubuntu system, which help tracking data collected in faculty online learning platform.
- Designing, setting and maintaining Faculty websites (especially projects funded by The Hong Kong Jockey Club Charities Trust).
- Establish Online Student Registration system for faculty events (front end and backend).

# Multimedia Web Designer (Research Assistant I)

The Centre for Information Technology in Education, the University of Hong Kong (09/2020 - 05/2021)

- Work independently in website production and development (Wordpress & Static html site).
- Design graphic artwork such as poster, certificate design and infographic illustration.

#### **EDUCATION**

Royal College of Art (RCA), London (09/2013 - 07/2015)

MA, Ceramic and Glass

Tsinghua University, Beijing (08/2009 - 07/2013)

BA, Ceramic Art and Design

### **COURSES & TRAININGS**

System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services

Coursera.org

The Complete PHP MYSQL Professional Course with 5 Projects

Udemy.com

Interactivity with JavaScript

Coursera.org

Advanced Styling with Responsive Design

Coursera.org